Selena Ramirez

123 Convoy St, San Diego, CA 12345 selenaramirez@exannple.com (123) 456-7890

A Customer Service Associate with two years of experience specializing in cash handling, PCS systems, communication, and inventory management. Adept at providing quality service to a diverse range of customers and supporting daily store operations.

Key Skills

- Customer Service
- Cash Handling
- ♦ Communication
- ♦ PCS System
- ♦ Inventory Management

Professional Experience

Gas Station Cashier

Exxon Mobil, San Diego, CA I April 2021 - Present

- Provide outstanding customer service to patrons for a high-volume gas station, identify opportunities to upsell car wash services and products, manage and balance cash register, and ensure compliance with opening and closing procedures
- Greeted and assisted gas station customers with sales transactions, ensured accurate cash handling and charges, and aided customers with disabilities in operating gas pumps
- Oversee daily stocking for store products, beverages, and food items and ensure adherence to safe storage and handling procedures

Gas Station Cashier

Shell, San Diego, CA j June 2020-April2021

- Assisted customers with operation of gas pumps, resolved issues with transactions, and alerted maintenance technicians to issues related to gas station pumps
- Coordinated with the store manager to open and close the gas station, which included receiving daily food and beverage product shipments and ensuring accurate counts

Education

High School Diploma

West View High, San Diego, CA September 2016 - June 2020